hip2save.com 2019-12-25

# Privacy Policy - Hip2Save

  1. **Privacy Policy**

LAST UPDATED ON November 12, 2018

This Privacy Policy is in all respects subject to and governed by the Hip2Save TERMS OF USE & AFFILIATE DISCLOSURE available [here](https://hip2save.com/about-me/disclosure-policy). Do not use our site or services if you do not agree with this Privacy Policy or the TERMS OF USE & AFFILIATE DISCLOSURE.

At Hip2Save, we are committed to protecting your privacy – as a first-time visitor or regular reader of this website. To our readers, we offer this pledge:

We will not sell, disseminate, disclose, transmit, transfer, share, lease, or rent any personally identifiable information or Personal Data to any third party not specifically authorized by you to receive your information except as we have disclosed to you in this Privacy Policy and in our Legal Notice. Under this Privacy Policy, you have the right to rectification if any of your Personal Data is incomplete or inaccurate, and the right of access to your Personal Data at any time to obtain free information about, and an exportable copy of, your stored Personal Data. You also have the right to erasure—the “Right to be Forgotten”—meaning we will delete your Personal Data if you request us to do so. Our contact information is below.

**The Information We Collect About You and How We Use It**

When you enter our website, we automatically collect, process and store certain information (which may include Personal Data) such as:

  * Your IP address and domain name.
  * The type of browser and operating system you use.
  * The time and length of your visit.
  * The pages of our site you visit.

This information is used for administrative and technical purposes. Such purposes could include counting the number of visitors to our site and individual pages within the site, determining referral sources to our website, assessing the technology used to access our site, and assisting with site maintenance. We protect and secure your Personal Data and take reasonable steps:

  * to protect data against accidental loss
  * to prevent unauthorised access, use, destruction or disclosure
  * to ensure business continuity and disaster recovery
  * to restrict access to personal information
  * to conduct privacy impact assessments in accordance with the law and your business policies
  * to train staff and contractors on data security
  * to manage third party risks, through use of contracts and security reviews

**Information Collection**

When you send us an email, subscribe to email updates for Hip2Save, or register on Hip2Save, you will provide us with certain personally identifiable information and Personal Data including your email address. When you register, we request username, email and password. To make comments, you will be asked to supply name or nickname, email address, and website (not required). It is your right to decline to provide us with Personal Data attendant to using any of our services, but if you do some, certain site features and functionality may not be available to you.

**Data Retention**

We will retain your Personal Data for only as long as your account is open or for only as long as needed for our purposes, unless otherwise required by law. We will retain and use information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements as follows:

  * the contents of closed accounts are deleted within 3 months of the date of closure;
  * backups are kept for 3 months;
  * billing information is retained for a period of 7 years as of their provision to Hip2Save in accordance with United States accounting and taxation laws; and
  * information on legal transactions between you and Hip2Save is retained for a period of 10 years as of their provision to Hip2Save.

**Cookies**

A cookie is a piece of data that is stored on a visitor’s hard drive while visiting Hip2Save. We use cookies to identify one unique visitor from another visitor, to store a visitor’s preferences, and to record session information in order to provide customized webpage content and better service when a visitor returns.

**Third-Party Links and Advertising**

Hip2Save may contain third-party advertising and links to third-party websites that are not controlled by Hip2Save. The third-party advertising and links are made available to our readers as a convenience. Please be aware that Hip2Save is not responsible for the content of third-party advertising and websites, nor are we responsible for the privacy policy or practices of third-parties and their websites. Our Privacy Policy only applies to information we collect from you while you are actively in session with Hip2Save. If you should link to a third-party website from Hip2Save, we strongly encourage you to review and become familiar with that website’s privacy policy.

Third-party advertisers may place cookies on your browser to collect data (not your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please see [here](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/#!/).

**Third-Party Services**

From time to time, we may engage third-parties to assist in providing marketing, back-end, programming and support services. These third-parties will only have access to information to the extent necessary to provide such services.

**No Disclosure of Personal Information**

Except as specified above, we do not intend to disclose any personal information about you to any third-party without prior consent unless we have a good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (i) complete your transaction; (ii) comply with legal process or other legal requirements of any governmental authority; (iii) protect and defend our rights or property; and (iv) enforce the terms and conditions on Hip2Save. We may provide certain information in aggregate form collected from you, and relating to you, to third-parties. However, we will not provide any personally identifying information.

**Postings**

We have no control over who reads your postings, or what other users may do with the information you voluntarily post, so please use caution when posting any personal information or comments.

**Business Transfer**

We intend to keep doing what we do for you. Although we have no plans to transfer Hip2Save, if that were to happen, we may share your information in a business transfer. As with any other business, we could merge with, or be acquired by another company. If this occurs, the successor company would perhaps acquire the information we maintain, including personally identifiable information and Personal Data.

**Changes in Our Privacy Policy**

We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time by posting the revised Privacy Policy in the “Privacy Policy” section of the website. The revised Privacy Policy is effective immediately when posted on Hip2Save. It is the responsibility of each user to review the website and the Privacy Policy periodically to learn of any revisions to this Privacy Policy. Your continued use of the website after the effectiveness of such revisions will constitute your acknowledgment and acceptance of the terms of the revised Privacy Policy.

**Important Note:** Any correspondence with Hip2Save or submission of content to Hip2Save, including documentation and images, is considered property of Hip2Save. Hip2Save reserves the right to reproduce such content, in whole or in part, and to use it in any manner, including allowing third parties to republish the material. In submitting something to Hip2Save, you are representing that the content belongs to you, does not infringe on any third party’s rights – copyright, trademark, privacy rights and the like – and is not libelous or unlawful in any other way.

**Questions**  
If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy or wish to contact us regarding your Personal Data, please feel free to contact us at:

Whittaker & Associates, Inc.  
c/o Hip2Save  
155 E. 50th Street Suite A  
Boise, ID 83714  
Email: bryn@hip2save.com

_This policy was lasted updated on November 12, 2018  _
